<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Evento</title>
    <description>Simple Jekyll theme to host internal/external events happening in and around your area. Free free to contribute or fork the repo.
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 07:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 07:20:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.5.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bitcoin Cash Block Production Accelerates as Mining Difficulty Adjusts</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After a slow start, blocks on the newly launched bitcoin cash blockchain are now being mined more frequently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the cryptocurrency originally split from the main bitcoin blockchain earlier this week, blocks were crawling in, with the first one taking about five hours to find and another taking nearly 13 hours. This came as no surprise to many, since bitcoin cash has much less mining power (with only a few groups, ViaBTC, Bitcoin.com and other unknowns securing the new blockchain).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But since blocks on the bitcoin blockchain are generated roughly every 10 minutes, some onlookers derided the new cryptocurrency for this initial roadblock, one that made it more difficult for users to send transactions or exchange bitcoin cash for other cryptocurrencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, block speeds have since picked up a bit. Today, for example, there’s been roughly one block per hour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This change is directed by an automatic adjustment of the difficulty (a function that regulates how easy it is for miners to generate new cryptocurrency tokens). Bitcoin cash’s difficulty has adjusted since it first broke off Tuesday, so miners are now having an easier time finding blocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Colorful blocks image via Shutterstock&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/event/bitcoin-cash-block-production-accelerates-as-mining-difficulty-adjusts.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/event/bitcoin-cash-block-production-accelerates-as-mining-difficulty-adjusts.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>OTC Trade Group: Blockchain Smart Contracts Could Spark Interpretation Challenges</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Smart contracts may only see limited real-world applications in the near future, according to a new research paper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The paper, released by the International Swaps and Derivatives Association (a New York-based trade group for over-the-counter derivatives firms) and London-based law firm Linklaters LLP, casts a broad overview on smart contracts and distributed ledger tech. The ISDA, formed in the 1980’s, counts more than 800 firms among its membership, according to the group’s website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It notably posits that the use of such contracts, which are self-executing pieces of code tied to certain conditions, are more likely to be used only in particular instances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The paper’s authors argue:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Certain operational clauses within legal contracts lend themselves to being automated. Other non-operational clauses – for instance, the governing law of a contract – are less susceptible to being expressed in machine-readable code. Some legal clauses are subjective or require interpretation, which also creates challenges.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Operational clauses, according to the paper, refer to more objective legal actions, for example one that requires a payment on a certain date based on an amount calculated by the nature of a work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It is assumed the most likely implementations of smart contracts in the near term will relate to operational clauses…rather than to non-operational clauses,” the report reads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Non-operational clauses, on the other hand, are more subjective to human interpretations, such as when the law should be applied under certain conditions. The paper’s authors state that in their view, programmable contracts bay not be able to account for the subjective nuances that exist in human interpretation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“For example, if an event of default occurs under an ISDA Master Agreement, this gives the non-defaulting party the right to terminate outstanding transactions. But the non-defaulting party might decide it does not want to exercise such a termination right at that time…depending on the commercial and relationship context at the time of the event, the nature of the default, and other external factors,” the paper noted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But even within those operational clauses, the authors suggest that a more standardized definition of complicated terms and activities need to be outlined before the smart contracts can be put into work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This would require those actions – for instance, payments and deliveries – to be represented in a more formal, standard way within the ISDA Definitions, enabling them to be read by machines,” the paper concluded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contract image via Shutterstock&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 1rem;&quot;&gt;The full ISDA paper can be found below:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/event/otc-trade-group-blockchain-smart-contracts-could-spark-interpretation-challenges.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/event/otc-trade-group-blockchain-smart-contracts-could-spark-interpretation-challenges.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Four Quadrants – Dividing and Conquering the Crypto Universe</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Just a quick introduction into AWS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please come along if your interested. Pizza will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/event/four-quadrants-dividing-conquering-crypto-universe.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/event/four-quadrants-dividing-conquering-crypto-universe.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Bitcoin Cash Price: Questions, Answers and More Questions</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Just a quick introduction into AWS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please come along if your interested. Pizza will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/event/bitcoin-cash-questions-answers-questions.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/event/bitcoin-cash-questions-answers-questions.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bitcoin Price Surges Past $3,200 to Hit All-Time High</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Just a quick introduction into AWS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please come along if your interested. Pizza will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/event/bitcoin-cash-questions-answers-questions.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/event/bitcoin-cash-questions-answers-questions.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chart, Learn and Explore: CoinDesk Launches ICO Tracking Tool</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Just a quick introduction into AWS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please come along if your interested. Pizza will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/event/bitcoin-cash-questions-answers-questions.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/event/bitcoin-cash-questions-answers-questions.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>'Every Token Is a Snowflake': Why the SEC's ICO Guidance Isn't Enough</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Just a quick introduction into AWS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please come along if your interested. Pizza will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/event/every-token-snowflake-secs-ico-guidance-isnt-enough.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/event/every-token-snowflake-secs-ico-guidance-isnt-enough.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bitcoin Fork Blues? These New Yorkers Threw a Party</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Just a quick introduction into AWS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please come along if your interested. Pizza will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/event/bitcoin-fork-blues-new-yorkers-threw-party-instead.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/event/bitcoin-fork-blues-new-yorkers-threw-party-instead.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
